scambusters.org 2018-06-02

# Privacy Policy.html

## 1\. HOW WE PROTECT YOUR PRIVACY.

This privacy policy tells you how we collect, use, and protect your personal information. By visiting our website, you accept and agree to the terms and conditions of this privacy policy. In particular, you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this privacy policy.

## 2\. MINORS.

We do not provide services or sell products to children. If you are below the age of 18, you may use our website only with the permission and active involvement of a parent or legal guardian. If you are a minor, please do not provide us or other website visitors with any personal information.

## 3\. PRIVACY POLICY IS PART OF OUR TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE.

Our privacy policy is part of, and subject to, our website’s terms and conditions of use. You may view these terms and conditions on our website.

## 4\. THE TYPE OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM YOU.

Like most places on the Internet, simply by visiting our website you automatically tell us certain information. This includes basic information such as your IP address, when you visited, the website from where you came prior to visiting us, the website where you go when you leave our website, your computer’s operating system, and the type of web browser that you are using. Our website automatically records this basic information about you. We may also collect any data that you provide us by posting it at our website or by email. You can always choose not to provide us with information. However, if you do withhold information, we may deny you access to some or all of our website’s services and features. Some transactions between you and our website may involve payment by credit card, debit card, checks, money orders, and/or third party online payment services. In such transactions, we will collect information related to the transaction as part of the course of doing business with you, including your billing address, telephone number, and other information related to the transaction.

## 5\. POLICY REGARDING ADVERTISING COOKIES

You’re able to access all of the pages at our website for free because this website is supported by advertising revenue. Data that we’ve collected over the years via emails we get from site visitors have clearly demonstrated to us that ads on our site actually help visitors solve their problems and gain the benefits they are looking for. Ads, in general, are problem solvers. Like many other websites, we may use cookies. In plain English, this means information that our website’s server transfers to your computer. This information can be used to track your session on our website. Cookies may also be used to customize our website content for you as an individual. If you are using one of the common Internet web browsers, you can set up your browser to either let you know when you receive a cookie or to deny cookie access to your computer. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services to you. Google is one of these third-party vendors, and uses cookies to serve ads on our website. Google uses a special DART cookie that enables it to serve ads to you based upon your visit to this site and others that you visit. If you don’t want to have this DART cookie on your computer, [you can opt out](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). We feel you’ll be making a mistake doing that, since you’ll then see random ads that won’t be of much use to you. But life is full of decisions and it’s your choice — we want to make it easy for you either way.

## 6\. WHAT WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION.

We use your information to operate our website’s business activities. For example, we may use this data to contact you about changes to our website, new services, or special offers, resolve disputes, troubleshoot issues, and enforce our website’s terms and conditions. As a general rule, we will not give your data to third parties without your permission. However, there are some important exceptions to this rule that are described in the following paragraphs. We may, in our sole discretion, provide information about you to law enforcement or other government officials for purposes of fraud investigations, alleged intellectual property infringement, or any other suspected illegal activity or matters that may expose us to legal liability. Although we do not disclose individually identifiable information, we may disclose aggregate data about our website’s visitors to advertisers or other third parties for marketing and promotional purposes. From time to time, we may use third party suppliers to provide services on our website. If a supplier wants to collect information about you, you will be notified. However, you will never be required to give information to a third party supplier. We restrict the way third party suppliers can use your information. They are not allowed to sell or give your information to others.

## 7\. USER NAMES AND PASSWORDS.

Your access to parts of our website may be protected by a user name and a password. Do not give your password to anyone. If you enter a section of our website that requires a password, you should log out when you leave. As a safety precaution, you should also close out of your web browser completely and re-open it before viewing other parts of the Internet.

## 8\. YOUR USE OF INFORMATION AND UNSOLICITED JUNK EMAIL.

If you obtain personally identifiable information about another website user, you are not allowed to disclose this information to anyone else without the consent of the user and our consent too. We hate junk email (Spam). Information you obtain from our website about us or other site users cannot be used by you or others to send unsolicited commercial email or to send unsolicited commercial communications via our website’s posting or other communication systems.

## 9\. YOUR VOLUNTARY DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES WHO ARE NOT OUR SUPPLIERS.

If you click on a link and go to another site, you will be subject to the third parties’ privacy policies. While we support the protection of privacy on the Internet, Simply Smarter Inc. can’t control how other people behave. We encourage you to read the posted privacy policy statement at any Web site where you are thinking of giving any personal info at all. If you choose to provide personal information to website visitors or other third parties who are not our suppliers, we recommend you please use caution when doing so. The privacy policies and customs of these third parties determine what is done with your information.

## 10\. YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION IN A BUSINESS TRANSFER.

Every business nowadays should plan for the possibility that it might sell certain or all of its assets to another company or individual, or that it might buy certain assets of another company or individual. In such transactions, customer and subscriber information generally is one of the business assets that is transferred or sold. Please review this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service to understand what options you have under these circumstances.

## 11\. AUTORESPONDERS.

We may use autoresponders to communicate with you by email. To protect your privacy, we use a verified opt-in system for such communications and you can always opt-out of such communications using the links contained in each autoresponder message. If you have difficulties opting out, you may contact us by email, or sending us mail to the address listed below.

## 12\. POLICY CHANGES.

The terms of this policy may change from time to time, and we will post these changes on this page. If you are concerned about the topic covered by this policy, you should read it each time before you use our website. Any questions or concerns about this policy should be brought to our attention by email and providing us with information relating to your concern. You may also mail your concerns to us at the following address:

_Simply Smarter, Inc. * 207 New Market Center #115 * Boone NC 28607 USA_

Our goal is that you always should be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

## 13\. CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS.

If you are a California resident and our customer, Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.83 permits you to request certain information about our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To request this information, please send an email or write us at the following address:

_Simply Smarter, Inc. * 207 New Market Center #115 * Boone NC 28607 USA_

## 14\. General Data Privacy Regulation (GDPR)

The GDPR takes effect on May 25, 2018, and is intended to protect the data of European Union (EU) citizens.

As a company that markets its site, content, products and/or services online we do not specifically target our marketing to the EU or conduct business in or to the EU in any meaningful way. If the data that you provide to us in the course of your use of our site, content, products and/or services is governed by GDPR, we will abide by the relevant portions of the Regulation.

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), or are accessing this site from within the EEA, you may have the right to request: access to, correction of, deletion of; portability of; and restriction or objection to processing, of your personal data, from us. This includes the “right to be forgotten.”

To make any of these requests, please contact our GDPR contact at GDPR@scambusters.org

## 15\. TELL US WHAT YOU THINK.

We want to know what you think. Simply Smarter Inc. welcomes any questions or comments you may have about privacy. Please send us an email at privacy at svr.com.

This policy was last updated on 5-21-2017.
